huh
HQ you actually think your life is worth
more than my pants I'll give you five
seconds to haul ass you leave my
boyfriend Bartleby out of this he is my
lover and I won't ever let you talk down
on him now he's acting like my bro that
is unforgivable hey Santa do you want to
know what this baseball bat is for it's
going right up your ass
what the [ __ ] oh my God they have c-3po
man this [ __ ] is bitchin
I can't believe they actually got this
oh yeah and look about your problem why
not just get a combo pack oh you're
still here
I was putting on my makeup damn this
conversation is getting almost as long
as your sagging boobs I was actually
just on my way to the SPO store name or
a team image what is this lovely ho Enix
unhand me [ __ ] my hair is not fake
unlike that fucked-up ass of yours oh my
God how do you even sit down so Mindy
were you able to find what you needed
yes Daddy thank you for bringing me here
today
you're the best cereal why thank you
very much I would love that
nothing beats a meal between France
uh-oh whoa my hello miss you got it
you've got such big boobs I'm sorry if I
sounded sad nervous